//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
        {
            numb: 1,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'あ' make?",
            answer: "a",
            options: ["i", "u", "e", "a"]
        },
        {
            numb: 2,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'い' make?",
            answer: "i",
            options: ["e", "i", "a", "o"]
        },
        {
            numb: 3,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'う' make?",
            answer: "u",
            options: ["u", "a", "i", "e"]
        },
        {
            numb: 4,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'え' make?",
            answer: "e",
            options: ["i", "e", "o", "a"]
        },
        {
            numb: 5,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'お' make?",
            answer: "o",
            options: ["e", "i", "o", "u"]
        },
        {
            numb: 6,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'か' make?",
            answer: "ka",
            options: ["ko", "ka", "ki", "ke"]
        },
        {
            numb: 7,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'き' make?",
            answer: "ki",
            options: ["ka", "ku", "ki", "ko"]
        },
        {
            numb: 8,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'く' make?",
            answer: "ku",
            options: ["ke", "ko", "ku", "ki"]
        },
        {
            numb: 9,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'け' make?",
            answer: "ke",
            options: ["ka", "ke", "ki", "ku"]
        },
        {
            numb: 10,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'こ' make?",
            answer: "ko",
            options: ["ke", "ka", "ko", "ku"]
        },
        {
            numb: 11,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'さ' make?",
            answer: "sa",
            options: ["sa", "shi", "su", "so"]
        },
        {
            numb: 12,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'し' make?",
            answer: "shi",
            options: ["sa", "shi", "su", "se"]
        },
        {
            numb: 13,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'す' make?",
            answer: "su",
            options: ["shi", "se", "su", "so"]
        },
        {
            numb: 14,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'せ' make?",
            answer: "se",
            options: ["sa", "se", "so", "shi"]
        },
        {
            numb: 15,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'そ' make?",
            answer: "so",
            options: ["sa", "su", "se", "so"]
        },
        {
            numb: 16,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'た' make?",
            answer: "ta",
            options: ["ta", "chi", "tsu", "te"]
        },
        {
            numb: 17,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'ち' make?",
            answer: "chi",
            options: ["chi", "tsu", "ta", "te"]
        },
        {
            numb: 18,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'つ' make?",
            answer: "tsu",
            options: ["te", "tsu", "to", "ta"]
        },
        {
            numb: 19,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'て' make?",
            answer: "te",
            options: ["ta", "te", "to", "tsu"]
        },
        {
            numb: 20,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'と' make?",
            answer: "to",
            options: ["ta", "te", "to", "chi"]
        },
        {
            numb: 21,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'な' make?",
            answer: "na",
            options: ["na", "ni", "nu", "ne"]
        },
        {
            numb: 22,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'に' make?",
            answer: "ni",
            options: ["na", "ni", "ne", "no"]
        },
        {
            numb: 23,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'ぬ' make?",
            answer: "nu",
            options: ["na", "nu", "ne", "ni"]
        },
        {
            numb: 24,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'ね' make?",
            answer: "ne",
            options: ["no", "ni", "na", "ne"]
        },
        {
            numb: 25,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'の' make?",
            answer: "no",
            options: ["na", "ni", "no", "ne"]
        },
        {
            numb: 26,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'は' make?",
            answer: "ha",
            options: ["hi", "ha", "fu", "he"]
        },
        {
            numb: 27,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'ひ' make?",
            answer: "hi",
            options: ["ho", "he", "hi", "ha"]
        },
        {
            numb: 28,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'ふ' make?",
            answer: "fu",
            options: ["fu", "he", "ho", "ha"]
        },
        {
            numb: 29,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'へ' make?",
            answer: "he",
            options: ["he", "ho", "fu", "hi"]
        },
        {
            numb: 30,
            question: "What sound does the Hiragana character 'ほ' make?",
            answer: "ho",
            options: ["hi", "ho", "he", "ha"]
        }
    ];
    
    
